Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative records [legacy series], 1947-1980; Series 2
  - Scholarships and awards, 1952-1978; Series 2 Subseries 4
    - D.C. Department of Recreation, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Dean's Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Dunbar High School Alumni Scholarship, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Ford Foundation, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Giddings School, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Graduation Awards and Prizes, 1971-1975; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Graduation Awards and Prizes, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Graduation Awards and Prizes, 1968-1969; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Graphics Department Scholarship Fund, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Howard Foundation Fellowship, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Judge's Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Maryland Federation of Women's Club, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - National Capital Housing Authority Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - National Society of Arts and Letters, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Helen and Maxwell Obst Memorial Fund, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Sarah Pickens Roberts Memorial Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Ronheim Memorial Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Saturday School Awards-Statistics, 1970-1974; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Saturday School, 1978 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Saturday School, 1976 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Saturday School, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Saturday School, 1973 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Saturday School, 1973 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Saturday School, 1972 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Saturday School, 1972 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Saturday School, 1971 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Saturday School, 1971 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Saturday School, 1970 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Saturday School, 1969-1970; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Saturday School, 1968-1969; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Saturday School, 1967-1968; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Saturday School (Art in Ephemera Records), 1966-1967; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Saturday School (Art in School Ephemera Records), 1965-1966; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Saturday School, 1964; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Sayre Scholarship Contribution (Saturday School), Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Kenneth Stubbs Memorial Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Student Council, 1972-1973; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Student Council, 1971-1972; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Student Council, 1970-1971; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Student Council, 1969-1970; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Summer School, 1971-1973; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Summer School, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Summer School, 1968; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Summer School, 1968; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Summer School, 1967; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Mary Lay Thom Sculpture Prize, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Visual Communications Department Award, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Eugen Weisz Memorial Scholarship, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Women's Committee, 1974-1975/1975-1976; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Women's Committee, 1973-1974; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Women's Committee, 1972-1973; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Women's Committee, 1971-1972; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Women's Committee, 1970-1971; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Women's Committee, 1969-1970; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Women's Committee, 1968-1969; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Women's Committee, 1967-1968; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Women's Committee, 1966-1967; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Women's Committee, 1965-1966; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Women's Committee, 1961-1965; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1975; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications A-D, 1974 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications E-H, 1974 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications I-Q, 1974 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications R-S, 1974 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications T-Z, 1974 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Miscellaneous- Lists and Statistics, 1974 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications A-C, 1973 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications D-J, 1973 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications K-S, 1973 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications T-Z, 1973 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous- Lists and Statistics, 1973 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications A-E, 1973 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications F-Q, 1973 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications R-Z, 1973 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous- Lists and Statistics, 1973 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications A-K, 1972 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications L-Z, 1972 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications A-L, 1972 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications M-Z, 1972 Spring; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous- Lists and Statistics, 1972; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous- Applications A-Z, 1971 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous- Correspondence, Lists, Memoranda, Statistics, 1952-1971; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Administrative records, 1960-2013; Series 12
  Subseries 2 Faculty and staff, 1970-2004; subseries 3 Admissions, 1993-2012; and subseries 5 Bursar's office, 1996-2001; of this series are restricted, according to the specifications listed below. Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
  Subseries 2 Faculty and staff, 1970-2004: Personnel records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation.
  Subseries 3 Admissions, 1993-2012: Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation. Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
  Subseries 5 Bursar's office, 1996-2001: Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation. Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
  Organizaed in 7 subseries: Course syllabi and department programs, 1965-2005; Faculty and staff, 1970-2004; Admissions, 1993-2012; Accreditation and self-studies, 1960-2013; Bursar's office, 1996-2001; Academic affairs, 1997-2006; and General administrative file, 1962-2012.
  Additional Administrative records, processed by the Corcoran Archives during the initial 1983 processing project, are located in Series 2 Administrative records [legacy series], 1947-1980.
  Contains Administrative records of the Corcoran School of Art + Design transferred to the Corcoran Archives following the initial processing project in 1983. Materials include curriculum planning records, faculty files, application records, admissions office files, accredidation reports and self-study materials, bursar's office records, development and steering committee records, correspondence, facilities reports, and survey reports.
  - Course syllabi and department programs, 1965-2005; Series 12 subseries 1
    Additional course syllabi and department programs records, processed in 1983 during the initial processing of the Corcoran Archives, are located in Series 2 subseries 1 Course syllabi and department programs, 1949-1980.
    Contains curriculum planning materials, fine art department records, and select syllabi, transferred to the Corcoran Archives following initial processing of the archives in 1983. Materials date from 1965-2005.
    - Curriculum, 1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Curriculum Planning, 1968-1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Advertising Design Curriculum, 1968-1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Corcoran School: Curriculum Planning, 1967-1968; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Corcoran School: Curriculum & Space Planning, 1965-1968; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Barnes Foundation Field Trip, 1968 December; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Field Trip Approval Forms, 1969 Summer; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Summer Brochure - Copy and Class Time Slots, 1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - General File Summer School, 1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Class Lists Summer School, 1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Summer School, 1969; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folders 21-22)
    - Summer School, 1968; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Summer School - Children, 1968; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Summer School, 1968; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Corcoran School: Departments: Ceramics, 1965; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Corcoran College of Art and Design Course Syllabi Book A, 2002 Fall; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Corcoran College of Art and Design Course Syllabi Book B, 2002 Fall; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Syllabi, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Syllabi, 2004 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Syllabi, 2005 Fall; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Course Syllabi, 2006 Fall; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Course Syllabi, 2007 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Fine Art department - Interdepartment Delivery Envelope, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folders 1-6)
    - Fine Art department - Chairs, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Fine Art department - Board of Overseers Corocrann, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Fine Art department - Faculty Phone Numbers, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Fine Art department - Student/Faculty Phone Numbers, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Fine Art department - Risk Control, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Fine Art department - Portfolio Day Philly, 2003; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Fine Art department - Fine Art Concentrations, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Fine Art department - Course Enrollment, 2004 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Fine Art department - Dept Meeting, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Fine Art department - AFA, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Fine Art department - FA- General, 2003-2004; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Fine Art department - Sophomore Syllabus Stuff, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Fine Art department - Misc. Course & Workshop information, 2002-2003; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Fine Art department - Sophomore Core Spring, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Fine Art department - Program Planning Sheet Fine Art, 2000-2001; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Fine Art department - Program Planning Sheet Fine Art, 2001-2002; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Fine Art department - Scheduling, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Fine Art department - Scheduling, 2003 Fall; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Fine Art department - Extra Stuff for Scheduling, 2004 Summer; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Fine Art department - Summer Scheduling, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - Fine Art department - Syllabi, Curriculum, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - Fine Art department - New Worlds from Old: 19th-century Australian and American Landscapes, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - Fine Art department - Misc. Papers, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folders 1-2)
    - Fine Art department - Curriculum, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Fine Art department - My Notes, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Fine Art department - BFA Senior Exhibitions Fine Art (negatives), 1998; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Fine Art department - Carnegie Mellon Art Program information, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Fine Art department - Internships Smithsonian, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Fine Art department - Misc. Papers, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Fine Art department - Corcoran College of Art & Design Faculty, 1999 Fall; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Fine Art department - Ivan Jacob Witenstein Fine Art IV, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Fine Art department - Janis Goodman Fine Art III, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Fine Art department - Kurt Godwin Intermed Painting, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Fine Art department - Lee Haner Intro to Fine Art, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Fine Art department - William Willis Advanced Painting, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Fine Art department - Janis Goodman Advanced Drawing, 2003 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Fine Art department - Strategies of Criticism, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Fine Art department - FA budget & Planning, 1999-2000; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Fine Art department - 2nd Year, 1999; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Fine Art department - Old Purchase Orders, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Fine Art department - Program Planning Sheet Fine Art, 2002-2003; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Fine Art department - Faculty Promotion, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Fine Art department - Promotion Reappointment Doug Lee, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Fine Art department - Faculty Goals, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Fine Art department - Faculty Manual Promotions//Reappointments, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Fine Art department - Plan, 2003; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 25)
    - Fine Art department - Faculty Resumes Slides Etc., circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 26)
    - Fine Art department - Ivan Resume, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 27)
    - Fine Art department - Budget Expense Reports, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 28)
    - Fine Art department - Senior Syllabus, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - Fine Art department - Senior Statements, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 30)
    - Fine Art department - Schedules, 2004 Spring; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 31)
    - Fine Art department - Faculty, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 32)
    - Fine Art department - To John Dickson Internship Info, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 33)
    - Fine Art department - Jeff Spaulding Bucket Girl Sculpture, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 34)
    - Fine Art department - Andy Holtin, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 35)
    - Fine Art department - Corcoran Library, circa 1990-2005; Series 12 subseries 1 (Box 150, Folder 36)
  - Faculty and staff, 1970-2004; Series 12 subseries 2
    Personnel records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation. Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
    This subseries contains faculty files, including adjunct faculty, former faculty, and inactive faculty, as well as faculty evaluations. Records date from 1970 to 2004.
    Additional faculty and staff files, processed in 1983 during the initial processing of the Corcoran Archives, are located in Series 2 subseries 2 Faculty and staff, 1947-1981.
    - Adjunct faculty files B-W, 1970-1997; Series 11 (Box 78)
    - Faculty evaluations [Dean's office], 2005 Spring; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 115)
    - Faculty evaluations: Spring 1996-Fall 1998, Fall 1999, 1996-1999; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 94)
    - Faculty evaluations: Spring 1999, Spring 2000, 1999-2000; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 95)
    - Faculty evaluations: Fall 2000-Spring 2001, 2000-2001; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 96)
    - Faculty evaluations: Spring 2001-Fall 2001, Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 97)
    - Faculty evaluations: Fall 2001-Spring 2002, 2001-2002; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 98)
    - Faculty evaluations: Summer-Fall 2002, Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 99)
    - Faculty evaluations: Spring and Summer 2003, Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 100)
    - Faculty evaluations: Fall 2003, Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 101)
    - Faculty evaluations: Spring and Summer 2004, Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 102)
    - Faculty evaluations: Fall 2004, Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 103)
    - Faculty promotions, 1999-2002; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 85, Folders 22-26)
    - Former faculty, 1980-1999; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 57, Folders 1-51)
    - Former faculty, 1986-1990; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 44)
    - Former faculty, pre-1990; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 36)
    - Former faculty, undated; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 129)
    - Inactive faculty, A-K, 1980-1999; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 54, Folders 13-43)
    - Inactive faculty, L-Z, 1980-1999; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 55)
    - Inactive faculty, undated; Series 11 (Box 71)
    - Past faculty and staff reports, payroll, chairs council reports [Dean's office], 1987-2003; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 107)
    - Ranked faculty files: A-J, 1970-1997; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 76)
    - Ranked faculty files: K-W, 1970-1997; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 77)
    - Student evaluations, before 2005 September 1; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 123)
    - Student evaluations, before 2006 January 1; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 124)
    - Teaching appointments and contracts, 1964-1978; Series 12 subseries 2 (Box 50)
  - Admissions, 1993-2012; Series 12 subseries 3
    Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation. Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
    This subseries includes applicant files, general admissions office files, graduate admissions files, student artwork slides, and student surveys. Records date from 1993-2012.
    - Applicant files, before 1999 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 120)
    - Applicant files, 2005 Fall-2007 Spring; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 134)
    - Applicant files: A-D, before 2006 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 130)
    - Applicant files: Q-W, before 2006 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 137)
    - Applicant files: Pa-Za, before 2008 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 159)
    - Applicant files: C-G, before 2009 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 143)
    - Applicant files: Si-Sy, before 2009 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 145)
    - Applicant files: A-D, before 2010 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 144)
    - Applicant files: Di-Lo, before 2010 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 158)
    - Applicant files: J-M, before 2010 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 147)
    - Applicant files: M-S, before 2010 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 146)
    - Applicant files: Sa-Ya, before 2010 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 152)
    - Applicant files: Sh-Yi, before 2010 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 156)
    - Applicant files: Ab-Ma, before 2011 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 151)
    - Applicant files: Ma-Wa, before 2011 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 153)
    - Applicant files: Al-Fa, before 2011 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 154)
    - Applicant files: Ki-Ra, before 2011 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 155)
    - Applicant files, before 2012 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 165)
    - Applicant files, before 2012 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 166)
    - Applicant files, before 2012 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 167)
    - Applicant files, before 2012 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 168)
    - Applicant files, before 2012 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 169)
    - Applicant files, before 2012 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 171)
    - Applicant files: D-K, undated; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 141)
    - Applicant files: H-K, undated; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 142)
    - Applicant files: Ma-Zi, undated; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 157)
    - Applicant files: BFA Fall 2005 and Spring 2006: A-Z, 2005-2006; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 114)
    - Applicant files: BFA Fall 2005: Gar-Moo, Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 116)
    - Applicant files: BFA 2005: Mo-Th, Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 117)
    - General admissions files, before 2007 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 127)
    - General admissions files, before 2007 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 131)
    - General admissions files, before 2007 January 1; Series 12 subseries 3 (Box 132)